INDIAN TUTOR | FOUR-POSE WEBRTC SHOWCASE
ZERO CROSSFADE | DIRECT CUT AT 20 FPS
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
SILENT | ACTIVE LISTENING / EMPATHETIC
DIRECT CUT: NEUTRAL > LISTENER
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
DIRECT CUT: LISTENER > NEUTRAL
SILENT | SPEAKING DIRECT (NO AUDIO)
DIRECT CUT: NEUTRAL > SPEAKING
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
DIRECT CUT: SPEAKING > NEUTRAL
SILENT | LIGHT SMILE
DIRECT CUT: NEUTRAL > SMILE
SILENT | ACTIVE LISTENING / EMPATHETIC
DIRECT CUT: SMILE > LISTENER
SILENT | SPEAKING DIRECT (NO AUDIO)
DIRECT CUT: LISTENER > SPEAKING
SILENT | ACTIVE LISTENING / EMPATHETIC
DIRECT CUT: SPEAKING > LISTENER
SILENT | LIGHT SMILE
DIRECT CUT: LISTENER > SMILE
SILENT | SPEAKING DIRECT (NO AUDIO)
DIRECT CUT: SMILE > SPEAKING
SILENT | LIGHT SMILE
DIRECT CUT: SPEAKING > SMILE
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
DIRECT CUT: SMILE > NEUTRAL
TTS | EMPATHY REACTION
TTS | SPEAKING DIRECT
DIRECT CUT: EMPATHY > SPEAKING
TTS | NEUTRAL RETURN
DIRECT CUT: SPEAKING > NEUTRAL
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
TTS | LIGHT SMILE REACTION
TTS | SPEAKING DIRECT
DIRECT CUT: SMILE > SPEAKING
TTS | NEUTRAL RETURN
DIRECT CUT: SPEAKING > NEUTRAL